kgrams.org 2008-08-20

# K-grams -- Privacy Policy

K-grams, Inc. Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the K-grams, Incorporated website. We care about and are committed to honoring the safety and privacy of our visitors and members. This privacy policy, part of our overall Terms of Use covers personally identifiable information shared through the K-grams website. You may always access the latest version of this policy at www.kgrams.org.

Information Collection  
Users under 13  
Cookies  
Other Links & Their Privacy Policies  
Security  
Exceptions and Changes to the Policy  
Questions, Changes, or Updates

**Information Collection**

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send your data -- such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally, and we don't associate it with other personal information you may voluntarily share with us.

When you register for our newsletter or sign our guestbook, we ask for some personal information, such as your e-mail address. We also may collect personal information if you voluntarily provide it to enter to win a contest or submit content. For online contests we may ask for name, email address, physical address, telephone number, school name and zip code, and particular preferences (such as T-shirt size, etc.), but only for the purpose of administering the prizes/awards.

The information that we collect is for the sole purpose of administering the contest/s and awarding prizes/awards. It is available only to K-grams and those who provide services to our site or help us administer contests and sweepstakes. Our contests are open only to those over age 13. To be eligible to win, however, the parents of anyone under 18 must sign an affidavit of eligibility before the prize is awarded.

We occasionally send out an email newsletter to K-grams members to highlight special K-grams features and options. You can elect not to receive communications from us or from other parties, either when you register or by noting your preference in response to communications from us.

Our policy regarding this information is simple: except as provided in this statement, K-grams will not disclose, sell or rent any of the registration information you provide without giving you notice and an opportunity to refuse disclosure, except as required by law. We make an effort to include a link to the Privacy Policy wherever we ask you for personal information.

**Users under 13**

Children under 13 may not register for K-grams, enter our online contests or sweepstakes, or use any K-grams services that require personally identifiable information, unless we have written and signed parental permission. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected information from anyone under 13 without the appropriate permission, we will immediately remove that information. For questions or other issues regarding the protection of children's privacy, please contact us.

**Cookies**

Like most websites, we use small bits of data called "cookies" which are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies let us "remember" information about your preferences and passwords and allow you to move within our site without reintroducing yourself. In our effort to provide you services customized to your interests, we use cookies to keep and sometimes track information about you. We use cookies to: access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver better and more personalized services; estimate our audience size for our advertisers; track the number of entries in our promotions and contests and identify which areas of our site you have visited. We also analyze information obtained from cookies to evaluate our users' preferences and improve our programming.

K-grams and our advertisers may also use cookies to determine on an anonymous basis which advertisements users have seen and how users responded to them, but don't use such cookies to collect personally identifiable information unless you give us permission to do so. Similarly, K-grams and our advertisers may use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to collect anonymous advertising metrics and to deliver cookies related to such advertisements. 

You should also be aware that companies that advertise on our site might use their own cookies. This privacy policy does not cover how these companies use their cookies.

top  
**Other Links & Their Privacy Policies**

To make our site more valuable to our visitors, we offer some features in conjunction with other providers. Although we do try to link only with sites who share our philosophy regarding information collection, and who indicate they do not intend to sell or share data with third parties, we don't control the privacy policies of other sites.

Once you leave our servers (you can tell where you are by checking the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) or address in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you're visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site's homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information.

**Security**

Only authorized K-grams employees and consultants who work directly on the site and who agree to keep information secure can access personal information. Our servers are in a secure location. Since we only collect and retain limited personal information to begin with, and we don't sell or share it with third parties, we're confident that any information we do have is protected.

**Exceptions and Changes to the Policy**

We may use, retain, or disclose personal information if required to do so by law, to cooperate in a legal investigation, or to protect the integrity of the site. Our privacy policy will be updated to reflect changes in legislation or fair information collection standards, but we won't make any retroactive change in how we handle personal data unless required to do so by law.

**Questions, Changes, or Updates**

If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, or would like to update, access, or change your information, please contact:

You may also contact us at:

**K-grams, Inc.  
1024 Hill Street  
Ann Arbor, MI 48104  
734.647.9424**
